Guide to the Center for Jewish Living records, 1985-2015.
Center for Jewish Living records
- Alpha Subject Files
  - Weil, Gotshal and Manges, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 147)
  - Weiler, Jack D, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 148)
  - Weinberg Foundation, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 149)
  - Weiner, Harvey and Naomi, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 150)
  - Weiner, Robert J (Box 12, Folder 151)
  - Weingarten, Randi, 2011 (Box 12, Folder 152)
  - Weinstein, Craig, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 153)
  - Weinstein, Judith, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 154)
  - Weinstein, Michael, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 155)
  - Weinstein, Michael J, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 156)
  - Weinstock Vineyards, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 157)
  - Weishoff, Henry, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 158)
  - Weintrob, Barry and Sheila, 2015 (Box 12, Folder 159)
  - Weiss, Rabbi Avi, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 160)
  - Weiss, Eugene, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 161)
  - Weiss, Prof. John H, 2011-2013 (Box 12, Folder 162)
  - Weiss, Stephen H, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 163)
  - Weiss, Morry, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 164)
  - Weiss, Patricia S, 2014 (Box 12, Folder 165)
  - Wessels, Arnols, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 166)
  - Wexner, Leslie H, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 167)
  - Whalen, James J, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 168)
  - Whitman, Christine, 1991, 2015 (Box 12, Folder 169)
  - Wien, Malkin, and Bettex, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 170)
  - Wiggins, Walter, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 171)
  - Wilcox, John, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 172)
  - Wile, Julius, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 173)
  - Wiles, Stephanie, 2014 (Box 12, Folder 174)
  - Williams, Jerome, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 175)
  - Williamson, Michael, 2011 (Box 12, Folder 176)
  - Wiseman, Ron (Box 12, Folder 177)
  - The Robert Wishnick Foundation, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 178)
  - University of Wisconsin, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 179)
  - Wojnilower, Albert, 1987-1989 (Box 12, Folder 180)
  - Wolfran, Chandra, 1989-1991 (Box 12, Folder 181)
  - Wolfson, Lev, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 182)
  - Worchel, Herbert and Karen, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 183)
  - World Zionist Organization, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 184)
  - Woolworth Co, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 185)
  - Woulk, Herman, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 186)
  - Wright-Riva, Colleen, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 187)
  - Wright, Michael, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 188)
  - Wunderlich, Martin, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 189)
  - Yad Vashem Art Museum, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 190)
  - Yale University, 2015 (Box 12, Folder 191)
  - Yavitt, Joseph B, 2015 (Box 12, Folder 192)
  - Ben-Yehuda, Rabbi Eliezar (Box 12, Folder 193)
  - Yeh, Ryan, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 194)
  - Yeoh, Kim, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 195)
  - Yorkville, Synagogue, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 196)
  - Young Israel Newsletters, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 197)
  - Young Israel of Cornell Alumni, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 198)
  - Yadowitz, Bernard, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 199)
  - Zall, Robert and Mollie (Box 12, Folder 200)
  - Zaslaw, Neal and Ellen (Box 12, Folder 201)
  - Zax, David and Marcia, 2012 (Box 12, Folder 202)
  - Zee Medical Services, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 203)
  - Zeitz, Chaim, 1989-1991 (Box 12, Folder 204)
  - Zhang, Emily, 2011 (Box 12, Folder 205)
  - Zhe, James, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 206)
  - Zierler, Rabbi Lawrence, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 207)
  - Ziff, Herbert and Fanny, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 208)
  - Zim American Israeli Shipping Co, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 209)
  - Zischoltz, Gerald, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 210)
  - Zisman, Myron, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 211)
  - Zuckerman, Mortimer, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 212)
  - Zvineri, Michael, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 213)